<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jakarta City</string>
    <string name="destination_1">Monas</string>
    <string name="destination_2">Kota Tua</string>
    <string name="destination_3">Ancol</string>
    <string name="destination_4">Galeri Nasional Indonesia</string>
    <string name="destination_5">Bebek Kaleyo</string>
    <string name="destination_6">Mie Gang Kelinci</string>
    <string name="destination_7">Ayam Keprabon</string>
    <string name="destination_8">Bubur Mang Udin</string>
    <string name="destination_9">Perpustakaan Nasional</string>
    <string name="destination_10">Perpustakaan Izmail Marzuki</string>
    <string name="destination_11">Perpustakaan BPS</string>
    <string name="destination_12">Perpustakaan Belanda</string>
    <string name="destination_13">Taman Simanjuntak</string>
    <string name="destination_14">Taman Tebet</string>
    <string name="destination_15">Taman Sunter</string>
    <string name="destination_16">Velodrome Jakarta International</string>

    <string name="destination_1_description">Monas, short for Monumen Nasional, is an iconic landmark situated in the heart of Jakarta, Indonesia. This towering monument stands as a symbol of the nations fight for independence. Designed by renowned architect Soedarsono, Monas reaches a height of 132 meters, representing the year of Indonesias proclamation of independence, 1945. Visitors can ascend to the top of the monument to enjoy panoramic views of Jakarta. Surrounding Monas is Merdeka Square, a vast public space often used for events and gatherings. Monas also houses a museum in its base, showcasing historical artifacts and exhibits related to Indonesias struggle for independence. It is a popular destination for both locals and tourists alike, offering insight into Indonesias rich history and culture.</string>
    <string name="destination_2_description">Kota Tua, also known as Old Town Jakarta or Batavia, is a historic district in the northern part of Jakarta. This area was once the center of Dutch colonial administration in the 17th century and still retains much of its colonial charm. Visitors to Kota Tua can explore well-preserved colonial buildings, including the Jakarta History Museum, Wayang Museum, and Museum Bank Indonesia. The cobblestone streets are lined with cafes, art galleries, and souvenir shops, making it a bustling tourist destination. Kota Tua is also home to Fatahillah Square, a picturesque plaza surrounded by colonial buildings and street performers. Visitors can rent bicycles or take guided tours to explore the areas rich history and architecture. Its a must-visit destination for history enthusiasts and anyone interested in experiencing Jakartas cultural heritage.</string>
    <string name="destination_3_description">Ancol Dreamland, located along the Jakarta Bay waterfront, is a popular recreational complex offering a variety of attractions and activities for visitors of all ages. The highlight of Ancol is Fantasyland, an amusement park featuring thrilling rides and attractions inspired by fairy tales and fantasy worlds. Other attractions within Ancol include Atlantis Water Adventure, a waterpark with slides and pools, and Seaworld Ancol, an aquarium showcasing marine life from around the world. Ancol also boasts several beaches where visitors can relax, swim, or enjoy water sports such as jet skiing and banana boating. Additionally, Ancol offers a range of dining options, from casual beachside cafes to upscale restaurants serving seafood and international cuisine. With its diverse array of attractions and beautiful waterfront location, Ancol Dreamland is a favorite destination for families, couples, and tourists seeking fun and relaxation in Jakarta.</string>
    <string name="destination_4_description">Galeri Nasional Indonesia, situated in central Jakarta, is the countrys premier art gallery showcasing Indonesias rich artistic heritage. The gallery houses a diverse collection of Indonesian art spanning various periods, styles, and mediums. Visitors can admire traditional and contemporary paintings, sculptures, installations, and other artworks by renowned Indonesian artists. Galeri Nasional also hosts temporary exhibitions and cultural events, providing a platform for emerging artists and promoting dialogue about art and culture. In addition to its exhibition spaces, the gallery offers educational programs, workshops, and guided tours for visitors of all ages. With its mission to preserve and promote Indonesian art, Galeri Nasional Indonesia is a cultural hub and a must-visit destination for art enthusiasts and anyone interested in exploring Indonesias vibrant artistic traditions.</string>
    <string name="destination_5_description">Bebek Kaleyo is a culinary institution in Jakarta renowned for its delectable Indonesian-style grilled duck, known locally as Bebek Bakar. The restaurant offers a cozy dining atmosphere with traditional Indonesian decor and attentive service. Bebek Kaleyos menu features a variety of duck dishes prepared with flavorful spices and served with rice and side dishes such as sambal (chili paste) and fresh vegetables. In addition to grilled duck, the restaurant also serves other Indonesian specialties, including grilled chicken, fried rice, and seafood dishes. Bebek Kaleyo is a favorite dining spot for locals and tourists alike, offering authentic Indonesian flavors and generous portions at affordable prices. Whether youre craving tender grilled duck or exploring Indonesian cuisine, Bebek Kaleyo promises a satisfying dining experience that celebrates the rich flavors and culinary traditions of the archipelago.</string>
    <string name="destination_6_description">Mie Gang Kelinci is a popular noodle restaurant in Jakarta known for its delicious and affordable noodle dishes. The restaurants name, which translates to "Rabbit Alley Noodles," reflects its humble beginnings as a small noodle stall in a narrow alley. Despite its modest origins, Mie Gang Kelinci has gained a loyal following for its flavorful and satisfying noodle dishes. The menu features a variety of noodle options, including mie ayam (chicken noodles), mie goreng (fried noodles), and mie rebus (boiled noodles), all prepared with fresh ingredients and aromatic spices. The restaurants casual atmosphere and friendly service make it a favorite dining spot for locals looking for a quick and tasty meal. Whether youre craving classic Indonesian comfort food or want to try something new, Mie Gang Kelinci offers a satisfying noodle experience that wont break the bank.</string>
    <string name="destination_7_description">Ayam Keprabon is a well-known restaurant in Jakarta specializing in Indonesian-style fried chicken, or Ayam Goreng. Since its establishment, Ayam Keprabon has been serving up crispy and flavorful fried chicken dishes that keep customers coming back for more. The restaurants secret recipe involves marinating the chicken in a blend of aromatic spices before frying it to perfection. The result is tender and juicy chicken with a crispy golden crust thats bursting with flavor. In addition to its signature fried chicken, Ayam Keprabon offers a variety of traditional Indonesian side dishes, such as sambal (chili paste), tempeh, and tofu. The restaurants cozy atmosphere and attentive service make it a popular dining destination for families, friends, and solo diners alike. Whether youre craving a hearty meal or want to indulge in some tasty Indonesian cuisine, Ayam Keprabon promises a satisfying dining experience that celebrates the rich flavors and culinary traditions of the archipelago.</string>
    <string name="destination_8_description">Bubur Mang Udin is a beloved street food stall in Jakarta famous for its delicious chicken porridge, or bubur ayam. Located in a bustling neighborhood, Bubur Mang Udin has been serving up comforting bowls of bubur ayam to hungry customers for years. The secret to its success lies in its flavorful broth, made from simmering chicken, rice, and aromatic spices for hours until it reaches the perfect consistency. The porridge is then topped with shredded chicken, fried shallots, green onions, and a drizzle of sweet soy sauce, creating a harmonious blend of flavors and textures. In addition to its signature bubur ayam, Bubur Mang Udin also offers other traditional Indonesian porridge varieties, such as bubur ketan hitam (black glutinous rice porridge) and bubur kacang hijau (mung bean porridge). Whether you\re craving a warm and comforting meal or looking to explore the diverse flavors of Indonesian cuisine, Bubur Mang Udin offers a delicious and satisfying dining experience thats sure to leave you craving more.</string>
    <string name="destination_9_description">Perpustakaan Nasional (National Library) is the largest library in Indonesia, serving as the primary repository of the nations literary and cultural heritage. Located in central Jakarta, the library houses a vast collection of books, manuscripts, periodicals, maps, and multimedia materials covering a wide range of subjects and disciplines. Its collection includes rare and valuable works dating back centuries, as well as contemporary publications and digital resources. Perpustakaan Nasional plays a vital role in preserving Indonesias cultural heritage and promoting literacy and education throughout the country. In addition to its extensive collection, the library offers various services and facilities to the public, including reading rooms, research assistance, and digital access to its catalog and collections. With its commitment to knowledge and learning, Perpustakaan Nasional is a valuable resource for scholars, researchers, students, and anyone interested in exploring Indonesias rich literary and intellectual traditions.</string>
    <string name="destination_10_description">Perpustakaan Izmail Marzuki (Izmail Marzuki Library) is a cultural institution located in Central Jakarta, Indonesia. Named after the prominent Indonesian composer Izmail Marzuki, the library is dedicated to preserving and promoting Indonesian art and culture. It houses a comprehensive collection of books, manuscripts, periodicals, and multimedia materials related to Indonesian music, performing arts, literature, and visual arts. In addition to its extensive collection, Perpustakaan Izmail Marzuki hosts various cultural events, exhibitions, and performances throughout the year, showcasing the rich diversity of Indonesian arts and culture. The library also provides educational programs, workshops, and resources for artists, scholars, students, and the general public. With its commitment to celebrating and preserving Indonesias cultural heritage, Perpustakaan Izmail Marzuki serves as a vibrant hub for creativity, learning, and cultural exchange.</string>
    <string name="destination_11_description">Perpustakaan BPS (BPS Library) is the library of the Central Bureau of Statistics of Indonesia, located in Jakarta. It serves as a specialized resource center for statistical information, research, and data analysis. The librarys collection includes a wide range of publications, reports, journals, and databases related to economics, demographics, social sciences, and other fields of study. Researchers, policymakers, academics, and students rely on the BPS Library for access to reliable and up-to-date statistical data and analysis to support their work and decision-making processes. In addition to its collection, the library offers research assistance, training programs, and access to online resources and databases. With its focus on statistical information and research, the BPS Library plays a crucial role in promoting evidence-based policymaking, economic development, and social progress in Indonesia.</string>
    <string name="destination_12_description">Perpustakaan Belanda (Dutch Library) is a historic library located in Jakarta, Indonesia. Originally established during the Dutch colonial period, the library served as a repository of Dutch literature, culture, and knowledge. Today, it houses a collection of books, manuscripts, maps, and archival materials related to Dutch colonial history, language, literature, and culture in Indonesia. The librarys collection reflects the complex and intertwined histories of Indonesia and the Netherlands, providing valuable insights into colonialism, cultural exchange, and identity. In addition to its historical significance, Perpustakaan Belanda serves as a research and educational resource for scholars, students, and the general public interested in exploring Indonesias colonial past and its legacies. The library also hosts cultural events, lectures, and exhibitions to promote dialogue and understanding between different communities and perspectives. With its rich collection and cultural heritage, Perpustakaan Belanda continues to be an important institution for the study and appreciation of Indonesian-Dutch relations.</string>
    <string name="destination_13_description">Taman Simanjuntak (Simanjuntak Park) is a public park located in Tebet, South Jakarta, Indonesia. Named after the Indonesian national hero, Lieutenant General Abdul Haris Nasution, who was also known as Simanjuntak, the park offers a serene and green space for recreation and relaxation. Taman Simanjuntak features lush greenery, jogging tracks, playgrounds, and seating areas, making it a popular destination for families, joggers, and nature enthusiasts. The park also hosts various community events, sports activities, and cultural performances throughout the year, providing opportunities for socializing and community engagement. With its tranquil atmosphere and scenic surroundings, Taman Simanjuntak offers a peaceful retreat from the hustle and bustle of city life, inviting visitors to unwind and connect with nature.</string>
    <string name="destination_14_description">Taman Tebet (Tebet Park) is a public park located in Tebet, South Jakarta, Indonesia. Spread across a vast green space, the park offers a variety of recreational facilities and activities for visitors of all ages. Taman Tebet features jogging tracks, sports fields, playgrounds, and picnic areas, making it a popular destination for families, fitness enthusiasts, and nature lovers. The park is also home to a diverse range of flora and fauna, providing opportunities for birdwatching and nature photography. Additionally, Taman Tebet hosts community events, cultural performances, and art exhibitions, fostering a sense of community and cultural exchange. Whether youre looking to exercise, relax, or socialize, Taman Tebet offers a welcoming and vibrant environment for people to enjoy and connect with nature.</string>
    <string name="destination_15_description">Taman Sunter (Sunter Park) is a recreational park located in North Jakarta, Indonesia. Situated along the shore of Sunter Lake, the park offers stunning waterfront views and a tranquil atmosphere for visitors to enjoy. Taman Sunter features lush green spaces, jogging tracks, cycling paths, and playgrounds, making it a popular destination for outdoor activities and relaxation. The park is also home to a variety of recreational facilities, including basketball courts, soccer fields, and fitness stations, catering to visitors of all ages and interests. Additionally, Taman Sunter hosts cultural events, music concerts, and food festivals, providing opportunities for community engagement and entertainment. Whether youre looking to exercise, unwind, or socialize, Taman Sunter offers a scenic and vibrant setting for people to enjoy and connect with nature.</string>
    <string name="destination_16_description">Velodrome Jakarta International is a world-class indoor cycling track located in Rawamangun, East Jakarta, Indonesia. Designed to international standards, the velodrome features a smooth wooden track with steep banked curves, providing optimal conditions for track cycling competitions and training. The velodrome is equipped with state-of-the-art facilities, including seating for spectators, athlete facilities, and support services. In addition to hosting cycling events, the velodrome also offers recreational and fitness programs for cyclists of all levels, from beginners to professional athletes. Whether youre a competitive cyclist looking to train and compete or a recreational rider seeking a thrilling cycling experience, Velodrome Jakarta International offers a premier venue for track cycling in Indonesia.</string>
    <string name="travel_destination">Travel Destination</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="library">Library</string>
    <string name="park">Park</string>

</resources>